Hi, my name is Lauren with Makeup by Dodge and today I'm going to teach you how to do your makeup in five minutes flat.
So first let's think about the problem areas we have.
Essentially what you're trying to do when you do your makeup just in five minutes is to get out the door right?
And to go on with your day.
And you're trying to greet the world with a very even bright energetic kind of face.
So some problem areas that we might have is discoloration of the skin which is very normal among many women.
Not, not many women have porcelain skin so to try to even out your complexion you can have some tinted moisturizer.
Just swipe that all over your face or if you have some dark circles or some problem blemishes just go ahead and swipe some concealer under those eye, eyes where your dark circle and dab at those blemishes very precisely with your concealer and blend.
Make sure you blend.
Another thing to bring some more color, some more life to your face would to apply some bronzer.
But make sure your bronzer goes well with your skin.
The orange on the face just usually doesn't cut it.
When you apply your bronzer you could just sweep it on the, on the out skirts of your face by your hair line and bring it down your cheeks, maybe down on your jaw line.
Touch your chin.
Touch your nose.
Do it on the other side.
And so you don't even have to worry about breaking out the eye shadow you can use that bronzer or that blush if you wanted to put a little blush on instead of some bronzer.
And close your eyes please.
Just go ahead and sweep them across your eyes and that'll just tie your whole face in and bring in a little bit more life, and a little warmth to it.
Another thing you can do is just apply a little waterproof mascara if you don't want to have to worry about touching it up later.
Just curl your eyelashes if you have time, swipe on some mascara.
And to make you lips more youthful and a little juicier go ahead and put on some lip gloss.
Don't; don't go into the, the lip stick thing that takes a little bit more time and effort.
But just put a little lip gloss maybe some chap stick and you have a very sun kissed and youthful look just in under five minutes.